question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "AMC&#039;s &quot;The Walking Dead&quot;, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were "
                    "introduced to us in Season 1.",
        "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Greenland is almost as big as Africa.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Theodore Roosevelt Jr. was the only General involved in the initial assault on D-Day.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the TV series Red Dwarf, Kryten&#039;s full name is Kryten 2X4B-523P.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "California is larger than Japan.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "One of Barack Obama&#039;s United States presidential campaign slogan&#039;s was &quot;Yes We Can&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Undertale&quot;, the main character of the game is Sans.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named &quot;Atlas&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Donald Duck played the role of Bob Cratchit in Disney&#039;s 1983 adaptation of A Christmas Carol.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The video game &quot;Fuel&quot; has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Harry Potter series of books, combined, are over 1,000,000 words in length.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Full Metal Panic!, Whispered are those who are capable of creating Black Technology.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Python programming language gets its name from the British comedy group &quot;Monty Python.&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
